<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Catalogue 2.0</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_movie">ListMovie</string>
    
    <string name="title_frozen2">Frozen II (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_terminator">Terminator: Dark Fate (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_ford">Ford V Ferarri (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_abominable">Abominable (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_doctor">Doctor Sleep (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_count">Countdown (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_last">Last Christmas (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_addams">Addams Family (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_a">A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_charlies">Charlie\'s angel (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_playing">Playing with fire (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_thegood">The Good liar (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_midway">Midway (2019)</string>
    <string name="ov_frozen2">Anna, Elsa, Kristoff, Olaf and Sven leave Arendelle to travel to an ancient, autumn-bound forest of an enchanted land. They set out to find the origin of Elsa\'s powers in order to save their kingdom.</string>
    <string name="ov_terminator">An augmented human and Sarah Connor must stop an advanced liquid Terminator, from hunting down a young girl, who\'s fate is critical to the human race.</string>
    <string name="ov_ford">American car designer Carroll Shelby and driver Ken Miles battle corporate interference, the laws of physics and their own personal demons to build a revolutionary race car for Ford and challenge Ferrari at the 24 Hours of Le Mans in 1966.</string>
    <string name="ov_abominable">Three teenagers must help a Yeti return to his family while avoiding a wealthy man and a zoologist who want it for their own needs.</string>
    <string name="ov_doctor">Years following the events of "The Shining," a now-adult Dan Torrance must protect a young girl with similar powers from a cult known as The True Knot, who prey on children with powers to remain immortal.</string>
    <string name="ov_count">When a nurse downloads an app that claims to predict the moment a person will die, it tells her she only has three days to live. With the clock ticking and a figure haunting her, she must find a way to save her life before time runs out.</string>
    <string name="ov_last">Kate is a young woman subscribed to bad decisions. Her last date with disaster? That of having accepted to work as Santa\'s elf for a department store. However, she meets Tom there. Her life takes a new turn. For Kate, it seems too good to be true.</string>
    <string name="ov_addams">The eccentrically macabre family moves to a bland suburb where Wednesday Addams friendship with the daughter of a hostile and conformist local reality show host exacerbates conflict between the families.</string>
    <string name="ov_a">Tom Hanks portrays Mister Rogers in A BEAUTIFUL DAY IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD, a timely story of kindness triumphing over cynicism, based on the true story of a real-life friendship between Fred Rogers and journalist Tom Junod. After a jaded magazine writer (Emmy winner Matthew Rhys) is assigned a profile of Fred Rogers, he overcomes his skepticism, learning about empathy, kindness, and decency from America\'s most beloved neighbor.</string>
    <string name="ov_charlies">When a young systems engineer blows the whistle on a dangerous technology, Charlie\'s Angels are called into action, putting their lives on the line to protect us all.</string>
    <string name="ov_playing">A crew of rugged firefighters meet their match when attempting to rescue three rambunctious kids.</string>
    <string name="ov_thegood">Consummate con man Roy Courtnay has set his sights on his latest mark: the recently widowed Betty McLeish, worth millions. But this time, what should have been a simple swindle escalates into a cat-and-mouse game with the ultimate stakes.</string>
    <string name="ov_midway">The story of the Battle of Midway, told by the leaders and the sailors who fought it.</string>
    
    <string name="tv_title_thewalking">The Walking Dead</string>
    <string name="tv_title_mandalorian">The Mandalorian</string>
    <string name="tv_title_silicon">Silicon Valley</string>
    <string name="tv_title_watchmen">Watchmen</string>
    <string name="tv_title_his">His Dark Material</string>
    <string name="tv_title_crown">The Crown</string>
    <string name="tv_title_theend">The End Of F***ing World</string>
    <string name="tv_title_theman">The Man In The High Castle</string>
    <string name="tv_title_cloak">Cloak And Dagger</string>
    <string name="tv_title_mr">Mr. Robot</string>
    <string name="tv_title_back">Back To Life</string>
    <string name="tv_title_rick">Rick And Morty</string>
    <string name="tv_title_mrs">Mrs. Fletcher</string>
    <string name="tv_title_bless">Bless The Harts</string>
    <string name="tv_title_dublin">Dublin Murders</string>
    <string name="tv_title_agents">Agents Of Shield</string>
    <string name="tv_title_stranger">Stranger Things</string>
    <string name="tv_title_thehaunting">The Haunting Of Hill House</string>
    <string name="tv_title_timeless">Timeless</string>
    <string name="tv_title_thex">The X Files</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_thewalking">Sheriff Deputy Rick Grimes wakes up from a coma to learn the world is in ruins, and must lead a group of survivors to stay alive.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_mandalorian">The travails of a lone bounty hunter in the outer reaches of the galaxy, far from the authority of the New Republic.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_silicon">Follows the struggle of Richard Hendricks, a Silicon Valley engineer trying to build his own company called Pied Piper.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_watchmen">Set in an alternate history where masked vigilantes are treated as outlaws, Watchmen embraces the nostalgia of the original groundbreaking graphic novel of the same name, while attempting to break new ground of its own.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_his">Two children embark on a magical adventure through parallel universes.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_crown">Follows the political rivalries and romance of Queen Elizabeth II\'s reign and the events that shaped the second half of the twentieth century.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_theend">James is 17 and is pretty sure he is a psychopath. Alyssa, also 17, is the cool and moody new girl at school. The pair make a connection and she persuades him to embark on a road trip in search of her real father.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_theman">In a dystopian America dominated by Nazi Germany and Imperial Japan, a young woman discovers a mysterious film that may hold the key to toppling the totalitarian regimes.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_cloak">Two teenagers from very different backgrounds find themselves burdened and awakened to newly acquired superpowers while growing closer together every day.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_mr">Elliot, a brilliant but highly unstable young cyber-security engineer and vigilante hacker, becomes a key figure in a complex game of global dominance when he and his shadowy allies try to take down the corrupt corporation he works for.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_back">After 18 years behind bars, Miri Matteson returns home and stumbles back into adult life in the claustrophobic coastal town she once knew in this half-hour comedy series.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_rick">An animated series that follows the exploits of a super scientist and his not-so-bright grandson.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_mrs">A single mom whose son has moved out for college looks to begin a new life on her own.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_bless">A group of Southerners strive to live the American dream.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_dublin">Crime series based on the novel by Tana French</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_agents">The missions of the Strategic Homeland Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_stranger">When a young boy disappears, his mother, a police chief, and his friends must confront terrifying supernatural forces in order to get him back.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_thehaunting">Flashing between past and present, a fractured family confronts haunting memories of their old home and the terrifying events that drove them from it.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_timeless">An unlikely trio travel through time in order to battle unknown criminals and protect history as we know it.</string>
    <string name="tv_ov_thex">Two F.B.I. Agents, Fox Mulder the believer and Dana Scully the skeptic, investigate the strange and unexplained, while hidden forces work to impede their efforts.</string>
    
    <string name="tab_text_1">Movies</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">TV Shows</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Movie Catalogue</string>
    <string name="change_language_settings">Change Languange Settings</string>
</resources>
